https://myradiostore.com/privacy-policy/

SiriusXM Radio
Pixel Technologies, Inc.
Privacy Policy
MyRadioStore, Inc. Privacy PolicyMyRadioStore, Inc.a Satellite Radio Superstore CompanyWinter Park, Florida, USALegal InformationYour privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy discloses how MyRadioStore, Inc. (“MRS”) and its affiliates collect, protect, use and share personal information gathered about you, in conformance with the applicable law. All personal information is collected in a fair and non-intrusive manner, with your voluntary consent. Personal Information is not accessible to anyone outside the specific function for which it is collected. MRS respects the privacy of employees and job applicants, franchisees, development agents, MRS customers and other visitors to our websites who may choose to provide personal information. We recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of personal information that you provide to us. This Privacy Policy will assist you to understand what types of information we may collect, how that information may be used, and with whom the information may be shared.In an effort to comply with the law, and our commitment to protect your personal information, we provide the following, which discloses our policies.What type of information do we collect?Personal Information is any information concerning the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable individual. An identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. Personal Information shall include but is not limited to: identifying information such as name, home address, home telephone number, e-mail address, Social Security number, financial information and employment-related information such as may be found on resumes, applications, background verification information, or in employment references.MRS takes measures to maintain the confidentiality of your Social Security Number, to protect your Social Security Number from unlawful disclosure, and to limit access to your Social Security Number. MRS will not make your Social Security Number available to the general public, print your Social Security Number on any card, require you to provide your Social Security Number to access any products or services, transmit your Social Security Number over the Internet unless the connection is secure or your Social Security Number has been encrypted, or require the transmittal of your Social Security Number to access our Website without requiring additional authentication.We will not collect Sensitive Personal Information, except to comply with Affirmative Action data requirements. Sensitive Personal Information can include but is not limited to: information pertaining to gender, disabilities and veteran status.Cookies - Internet UsersIn addition to Personal Information, we use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain web pages to help analyze our web page flow and measure promotional effectiveness. Cookies are pieces of information a website sends to an individual’s hard drive while they are viewing the website. Cookies allow the website to remember important information that will make your visit to the site more useful. We use cookies to help improve your future visits. If you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or if you wish to turn off all cookies, use the options on your browser to assist you. The “Help” option on your browser may assist you in changing your cookie preferences. Please note that by turning cookies off, you will not have access to many features available on our website.Children and Data CollectionWe care about the safety of children. We will not knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children under 13 years of age are required to obtain the express permission of a parent or guardian before submitting any Personal Information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet.Our Use of Your InformationWe use your Personal Information to facilitate the services you request. We have tailored our Privacy Policy to adequately inform you of the use of your Personal Information.Collection and Use of Employee Personal InformationMRS also collects Personal Information from its employees and applicants (human resource data) in connection with administration of its Human Resources programs and functions. These programs and functions include, but are not limited to: job applications and hiring programs, compensation and benefit programs, performance appraisals, training, access to MRS facilities and computer networks, employee profiles, internal intranet employee directories, Human Resource recordkeeping, Affirmative Action data, and other employment related purposes. It is the policy of MRS to keep all past and present employee information private from disclosure to third parties. There are certain business related exceptions and they are:1.    To comply with county, state or federal agency requests;2.    Inquiries from third parties with a signed authorization from the employee to release the information, except in situations where limited verbal verifications are acceptable (see below);3.    Third parties with which MRS has contractual agreements to assist in administration of company sponsored benefits.Verification of EmploymentProspective employers, state agencies, financial institutions, and residential property managers routinely contact MRS requesting information on a former or current employee's work history and salary. All such requests of this type shall be referred to and completed on a confidential basis by the Human Resources Department or Payroll Department.For written verification of employment requests, information will be provided on the form only when it is accompanied by an employee's signed authorization to release information. The form will be returned directly to the requesting party and filed as part of the Human Resources or Payroll Department’s confidential records.Medical InformationMRS is compliant with federal HIPAA regulations and only utilizes information related to the company sponsored healthcare plan on a "need to know" basis for administration of the healthcare plan.Collection and Use of Customer InformationMRS will not collect customer Personal Information, unless the customer contacts MRS directly. In order to adequately address a customer’s concern. Failure to provide necessary information may prevent MRS from fully addressing any customer concerns.If you are a participant in the Online MyRadioStore, Inc. Store, we ask for contact information, name, shipping address, phone number, and e-mail address. In the future, we may use this information to contact you regarding products or promotions, as well as other products and services, which may be of interest to you. At any time you may “opt out” of future contacts by un-subscribing from our database or contacting the Privacy Officer.Sharing of Personal InformationWe may share Personal Information with our service providers, consultants and affiliates for our internal business purposes. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, MRS will not share Personal Information with a third party, unless a customer requests, consents to such disclosure, or disclosure is required or authorized by law. MRS reserves the right to disclose Personal Information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order legally requires or authorizes us to do so. MRS also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, or financing of all or any portion of MRS or of any of the business or assets or shares of MRS.Storage, Retention and Accuracy of Personal InformationMRS insures that Personal Information is safeguarded against loss, access, use, modification, disclosure or other misuse. All reasonable steps are taken to prevent unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Information.MRS will retain your Personal Information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws, and your consent to such purpose(s) remains valid after termination of our relationship with you.We take all reasonable steps to insure that your Personal Information is accurate, up-to-date, complete, relevant and not misleading.MRS may store your Personal Information in its databases located in the United States and/or other countries outside of the United States. Additionally, some of our service providers may reside in the United States or other countries outside of the United States and will be subject to the laws of the local jurisdiction. As a result, in certain circumstances, the United States and other foreign governments, courts, law enforcement agencies or regulatory agencies may be entitled to access the Personal Information collected and held by MRS.Contact InformationYou may contact the Privacy Officer to access, correct or delete your Personal Information. If necessary, the Privacy Officer will contact another employee to assist in completing your requested task.If you have any questions or complaints, please contact the Privacy Officer. The Privacy Officer can be reached by telephone at: 1-866-463-3396; by Facsimile at: (407) 657-8177; by email at: contactus@myradiostore.com; or by mail at MyRadioStore, Inc., 3302 Athena Drive Winter Park, FL 32792 USA. We will address your concern and attempt to resolve any problem.Links to Non-MRS Web Sites and Third PartiesPlease note that MRS or MRS web sites may contain links to other web sites for your convenience and information. MRS does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from www.myradiostore.com. MRS’s privacy policy cannot and does not apply to external Web areas. We do not endorse or make any representations about third party web sites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the MRS privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company or website before submitting your Personal Information. Some third parties may choose to share their personal data with MRS; that sharing is governed by that third party company’s privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you in this Privacy Policy, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
×
OK
×
